Thriller Night is a animation, music, horror film directed by Sean Bishop.
A Shrek parody of Michael Jackson's Thriller song
and music video, with Donkey singing.
Shrek (voice), played by Michael Gough.
Donkey (voice), played by Dean Edwards.
Princess Fiona (voice), played by Holly Fields.
Puss in Boots (voice), played by André Sogliuzzo.
Pinocchio / Three Pigs (voice), played by Cody Cameron.
Gingerbread Man (voice), played by Conrad Vernon.
Sleepless Night (French: Nuit Blanche) is a 2011 French-language action thriller film
directed by Frédéric Jardin, who co-wrote the story with Nicolas Saada.
The film stars Tomer Sisley, Adel Bencherif, Julien
Boisselier, Serge Riaboukine and Pom Klementieff.
Sleepless Night was premiered in 2011 at the Toronto International Film
Festival and  received positive reviews from critics.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.